A semi-realistic digital painting of a villainous dark elf mage, styled like a League of Legends splash art. The character, a 50-year-old man with dark grey skin and long black hair tied back, has a menacing and ominous expression. He levitates close to the ground amidst a stormy landscape that he has conjured with his magic. His eyes glow with a palette of colors matching the lightning he manipulates with his hands and from the sky. He holds a magical staff, intricately carved with elfic symbols and adorned with gems. His appearance includes wide, thick eyebrows, a trimmed beard, and a pointy mustache.
