A character inspired by Dark Elves, depicted in a semi-realistic style similar to League of Legends splash arts. This Dark Elf mage is a black person with short dreadlocked hair. He levitates close to the ground, wielding a magic staff carved with elven symbols and embedded with gems. He is using the staff to control lightning, invoking it from his hands and the stormy sky above. His eyes glow with a spectrum of colors that echo the vibrant lightning he manipulates. The surrounding landscape is dark and tempestuous, underlining the storm summoned by the mage's powerful magic.
